{
  "questions": [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "椅子",
        "answer": "chair",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "记忆能力"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "海关",
        "answer": "customs",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "抽象思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "书桌",
        "answer": "desk",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "记忆能力"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "护照",
        "answer": "passport",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "抽象思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "相同的",
        "answer": "same",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "记忆能力"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "新闻",
        "answer": "news",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "抽象思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "懒的",
        "answer": "lazy",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "记忆能力"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "工程师",
        "answer": "engineer",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "抽象思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "冰箱",
        "answer": "fridge|refrigerator",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "记忆能力"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "国籍",
        "answer": "nationality",
        "textbook": "NCE1",
        "keyPoint": "单词拼写",
        "ability": "抽象思维"
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "type": "单词",
        "question": "这些",
        "answer": "these",
        "textbook": "",
        "keyPoint": "代词",
        "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "红色的",
          "answer": "red|reddish",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "灰色的",
          "answer": "gray|grey",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "黄色的",
          "answer": "yellow|yellowish",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "黑色的",
          "answer": "black",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "橘黄色的",
          "answer": "orange",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "雇员",
          "answer": "employee",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "勤奋的",
          "answer": "hard-working|diligent",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "推销员",
          "answer": "sales reps|salesperson",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "词组",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "男人",
          "answer": "man|men",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "办公室",
          "answer": "office",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "助手",
          "answer": "assistant",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "事情",
          "answer": "matter",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "孩子们",
          "answer": "children|kids",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 25,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "累，疲乏",
          "answer": "tired",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 26,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "男孩",
          "answer": "boy",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 27,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "妈妈(儿语)",
          "answer": "mum|mom",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 28,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "坐下",
          "answer": "sit down",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "词组",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 29,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "口渴",
          "answer": "thirsty",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 30,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "好，可以",
          "answer": "right|ok|alright|fine|okay|good|well",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 31,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "冰淇淋",
          "answer": "ice cream",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "词组",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 32,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "大的",
          "answer": "big|large",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 33,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "小的",
          "answer": "small|little",
          "source": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 34,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "开着的",
          "answer": "open|opened",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 35,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "关着的",
          "answer": "closed|shut",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 36,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "轻的",
          "answer": "light|lightweight",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 37,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "重的",
          "answer": "heavy|heavyweight",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 38,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "长的",
          "answer": "long|lengthy",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 39,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "鞋子",
          "answer": "shoes|footwear",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 40,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "祖父，外祖父",
          "answer": "grandfather|grandpa",
          "textbook": "",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 41,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "祖母，外祖母",
          "answer": "grandmother|grandma",
          "textbook": "NCE1",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 42,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "私人的",
          "answer": "private",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 43,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "谈话",
          "answer": "conversation",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 44,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "剧场，戏院",
          "answer": "theatre",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 45,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "座位",
          "answer": "seat",
            "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 46,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "戏；玩，游戏",
          "answer": "play",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 47,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "大声地",
          "answer": "loudly",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "副词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 48,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "生气的",
          "answer": "angry",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 49,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "生气地",
          "answer": "angrily",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "副词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 50,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "注意",
          "answer": "attention",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 51,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "容忍",
          "answer": "bear",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 52,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "事；商业，生意",
          "answer": "business",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 53,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "无礼地，粗鲁地",
          "answer": "rudely",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "副词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 54,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "直到",
          "answer": "until",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "介词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 55,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "外面",
          "answer": "outside",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "副词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 56,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "(铃、电话等)响",
          "answer": "ring",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 57,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "姑母，姨母",
          "answer": "aunt",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 58,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "重复",
          "answer": "repeat",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 59,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "寄，送",
          "answer": "send",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 60,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "明信片",
          "answer": "postcard",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 61,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "毁掉",
          "answer": "spoil",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 62,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "博物馆",
          "answer": "museum",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 63,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "公共的",
          "answer": "public",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 64,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "友好的",
          "answer": "friendly",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 65,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "服务员，招待员",
          "answer": "waiter",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 66,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "借给",
          "answer": "lend",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 67,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "决定",
          "answer": "decision",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 68,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "整个的",
          "answer": "whole",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 69,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "唯一的，单一的",
          "answer": "single",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 70,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "令人兴奋的",
          "answer": "exciting",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 71,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "接受，收到",
          "answer": "receive",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 72,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "乐器，器械",
          "answer": "instrument",
          "textbook": "NCE2",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 73,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "单位、单元",
          "answer": "unit",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 74,
          "type": "单词", 
          "question": "部分，章节",
          "answer": "section",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 75,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "谈话，会话",
          "answer": "conversation",
          "textbook": "中考", 
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 76,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "铃，钟",
          "answer": "bell",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 77,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "瓶子",
          "answer": "bottle",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 78,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "橡皮擦",
          "answer": "eraser",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 79,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "钥匙",
          "answer": "key",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 80,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "东西，事物",
          "answer": "thing",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 81,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "需要",
          "answer": "need",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 82,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "乐趣，有趣",
          "answer": "fun",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 83,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "院子",
          "answer": "yard",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 84,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "胡萝卜",
          "answer": "carrot",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 85,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "鹅",
          "answer": "goose",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 86,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "人们",
          "answer": "people",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 87,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "早晨",
          "answer": "morning",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 88,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "班级",
          "answer": "class",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 89,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "名字",
          "answer": "name",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 90,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "再见",
          "answer": "goodbye",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "感叹词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 91,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "时间",
          "answer": "time",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 92,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "书包",
          "answer": "schoolbag",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 93,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "帽子",
          "answer": "cap",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 94,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "尺子",
          "answer": "ruler",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 95,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "铅笔",
          "answer": "pencil",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 96,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "红色的",
          "answer": "red",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 97,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "绿色的",
          "answer": "green",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 98,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "蓝色的",
          "answer": "blue",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 99,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "黄色的",
          "answer": "yellow",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 100,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "橙色的",
          "answer": "orange",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 101,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "黑色的",
          "answer": "black",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 102,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "白色的",
          "answer": "white",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 103,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "棕色的",
          "answer": "brown",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 104,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "颜色",
          "answer": "colour",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 105,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "自行车",
          "answer": "bicycle|bike",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 106,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "裤子",
          "answer": "trousers",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 107,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "床",
          "answer": "bed",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 108,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "书桌",
          "answer": "desk",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 109,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "椅子",
          "answer": "chair",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 110,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "猫",
          "answer": "cat",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 111,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "鞋子",
          "answer": "shoe",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 112,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "盒子",
          "answer": "box",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 113,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "一双，一对",
          "answer": "pair",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 114,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "妈妈",
          "answer": "mum|mom",
          "textbook": "中考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 115,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "令人尴尬的、难对付的",
          "answer": "awkward",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 116,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "初级的，地位低的",
          "answer": "junior",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 117,
          "type": "单词", 
          "question": "探索",
          "answer": "explore",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 118,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "自信的",
          "answer": "confident",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 119,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "信心",
          "answer": "confidence",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 120,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "向前的",
          "answer": "forward",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 121,
          "type": "短语",
          "question": "记笔记",
          "answer": "take notes",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "动词短语",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 122,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "闪光",
          "answer": "flash",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 123,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "组织",
          "answer": "organise",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 124,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "组织",
          "answer": "organization|organisation",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 125,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "目标",
          "answer": "goal",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 126,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "策略",
          "answer": "strategy",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 127,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "伙伴",
          "answer": "partner",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 128,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "改进",
          "answer": "improve",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 129,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "好奇的",
          "answer": "curious",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 130,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "公司",
          "answer": "company",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 131,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "个性",
          "answer": "personality",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 132,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "风格",
          "answer": "style",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 133,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "复习",
          "answer": "revise",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "动词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 134,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "青少年的",
          "answer": "teenage",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "形容词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        },
        {
          "id": 135,
          "type": "单词",
          "question": "青少年",
          "answer": "teenager",
          "textbook": "高考",
          "keyPoint": "名词",
          "ability": "词汇理解"
        }
  ]
} 